Only three days left till the new year.
And I hope you're all
enjoying your holiday.
Hey, were you up late again?
Yeah, for a mechatronics
project for school. Mecha-what?
Sounds fun.
Kazuto, you see this yet?
What the?!
The Holy Sword Excalibur
has been found in ALO?!
Oh man, that sucks.
I can't believe someone
else beat us to it.
Read the article, Doofus.
It says it's been found is all.
No one's actually got it yet.
Yeah, you're right.
Don't scare me like that.
A couple months ago on the Arun Plains,
Leafa, Yui, and me got swallowed
by a big-ass monster worm.
It dropped us in an underground
realm called Jotunheim.
We looked around for a bit and came
across this four-armed humanoid monster.
It was fighting another
monster that looked
like a cross between an
elephant and a jellyfish.
Go figure.
Leafa felt sorry for the jellyphant
thing and told me to go save it.
I lured forearms onto this frozen
lake and it fell through the ice.
Then the jellyphant took care of it.
Leafa decided to call it Tonki,
and suddenly it transformed into an even
weirder-looking thing with eight wings.
We hopped on its back and it took us to a
passageway, leading to the surface world.
On the way up was when we saw it.
An upside-down pyramid hanging
from the roots of the world tree.
And a long golden sword shimmering inside.
Excalibur.
I was planning on going back
for it someday, but now...
It'd be a nice break from all that
floor-clearing you're doing in New Aincrad.
This article doesn't say
anything about how they found it.
Players can't fly in Jotunheim, remember?
But that's the only way to spot Excalibur.
That thing's too high up to see.
Unless they rescued
one of Tonki's friends,
hitched a ride, and
triggered the quest flag.
If we could do it, so could someone else.
I guess that makes sense, although...
Who'd trust a creepy...
Uh, I mean, who'd trust such a unique
monster unless they had weird tape?
I mean, a weirdly big heart.
Someone just like you, sis.
What are the odds?
He's not creepy.
He's adorable.
Anyway, the whole point of showing
you that was to get you going.
It's only a matter of time before someone
grinds through that
dungeon and gets the sword.
You're right.
Clock's ticking.
So what are you going to do about it?
Sugu, getting rare items
isn't the point of it.
If that's all you play
for, you're missing out.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
There's funner things to
do than boosting stats.
I wasn't finished.
I think Tonki wanted us to find it, and
that's why he showed us where it was.
For some reason, he needs
us to clear that dungeon,
so it's up to us to
make his wish come true.
Tonki's our friend, and there's no
way I'm turning my back on a friend.
Ooh.
A minute ago, you called
your friend creepy.
I meant creepy cool.
Anyway, you in?
Sure.
I don't have practice
because of the holidays.
Awesome!
Okay, we'll need seven others.
We don't want to overload Tonki.
For starters, we got you, me, and Asuna.
Then there's Klein, Liz, and Silica.
We need one more person.
Eggiel's gotta work tonight.
Chris Height's not leveled up yet.
Rekon's grinding in Sylph territory.
Oh, I know!
Let's ask Xenon to come along!
Great idea, sis! What'd you expect?
I'll message him right now.
Except for Asuna.
I'll leave that to you. Okay.
I wish I could see Kirito again
before I go visit my grandparents.
Hi, Kirito!
Morning, Asuna.
Sorry to call so early.
We were planning on going on
a quest in ALO this afternoon.
You want to go?
Yeah, I'll totally go.
I'm free all day today.
Cool.
I'll text you the time and
place, so keep an eye out for it.
You know I will.
See you in a little while, then.
Yes!
So, I'll never forget that
I'm a man who flew away. .
I've been working for the
day that I've been doing,
but I've been working for a long time.
I'm not sure what's going on.
.
It's the end of the world.
It's the end of the story.
The story of the beginning.
It's the end of the song.
You can see the future.
The world is the one who is in
the sky. It's been a long time.
It's been a long time.
Oh, give it for my way.
Hey, Klein, do you get to
take vacation for New Year's?
Been on it since yesterday.
Even if I wanted to work and I don't,
there's no shipments this time of year.
You know what my cheap-ass boss said?
Be thankful you got a job where you
get a whole week off for New Year's,
bragging about it like
he was doing us a favor.
And speaking of favors,
if we do manage to snag Excalibur today,
How about doing me a solid and help me
get my hands on the Soul Blade Kaguzuchi?
Seriously?
That dungeon's like a freaking oven, man.
Yeah, well, I'm going
to Jotunheim for you,
where it's colder than
the ass end of an ice pop.
You know, I want something
out of this, too.
The Shekinah bow.
Your avatar's two weeks old, and already
you're gunning for a legendary weapon?
Yeah, well, that bow Liz
made me as great and all,
but I need something
with a little more range.
Oh, yeah?
Then what the heck are you
using a bow and A .L .O. for?
Their range falls between
the spears and magic.
You're like the only player who wants to
use these things to snipe from 100 meters.
If I had my way, I'd want
double that range at least.
We're back, guys!
Thanks for waiting.
We thought you were never
coming back. What's up?
You get lost or something?
Not at all.
We were gathering
information while we shopped.
We talked to a whole
bunch of people, Daddy,
and so far not one player or party
has reached that dungeon yet.
Really?
Well, then how the heck do
they know where Excalibur's at?
That's the thing, Daddy.
No one really knows where it is.
Apparently they found a different
quest than the one Tonki showed us.
They met an NPC who told them if
they finished this other quest,
they'd get Excalibur as the reward.
And from what we heard, the quest
they're going on isn't very pleasant.
Instead of a delivery quest or an
escort quest, it's a kill quest.
Just slaughtering monsters.
Everyone in Jotunheim is out there
right now killing as many as they can.
Yeah, that doesn't even sound
close to being pleasant.
This whole thing sounds
sketchy to me, guys.
Here's what we know.
There's a dungeon in the sky with
Excalibur locked up at the bottom of it.
To get to it, you gotta fight your
way through a bunch of monsters.
But now we got an NPC offering
it up as a kill quest reward?
That's bizarre now that you
mention it? That is weird!
The NBC is not showing anyone to the
dungeon, but that's where the sword is.
Well, I'm sure we'll find
out why once we get there!
Alrighty, your weapons are all
restored and ready for action.
Even though our party's full of hotness,
we're still a bunch of
gear-toting meatheads.
If you want to switch it up, you
could always boost your magic.
Ha! Keep dreaming.
A real samurai?
He wouldn't be caught dead using magic.
Code of Honor.
Code of Honor, huh?
Know what samurais are
classified as in RPGs?
They're both warriors and
black magic users. Please.
I'd rather bust my sword and quit
being a samurai than use magic, doll.
I don't know, Klein.
If I remember, Red, didn't you use
a flame sword skill the other day?
You know, when you activate
it, you are using part magic.
No way! Really?
Yes, Klein, what Silica said is true.
Remember the Mei update?
It brought a whole bunch
of new sword skills to ALO.
Some are physical and others
are advanced, like Earth, Water,
Fire, Wind, Dark, and Divine, all
of which are magical attributes.
Fire is magical too, huh?
Okay, ex-samurai, you need
help busting that sword?
Dude, back me up here.
Well, since you don't chant when using
sword skills, I guess it's not the same.
I'll let it slide this time.
I really appreciate you guys
helping me out on such short notice.
Seriously, you don't know
how much this means to me.
Alright, are you ready? Yeah!
God!
How many steps does
this thing have, anyway?
I know.
I bet the tower on the
dungeon floor of New
Ein Kirito doesn't even
have as many as this.
Oh, come on.
It's not that bad.
If we took the normal route to
Jotunheim, it'd take at least two hours.
This way, it's just five minutes.
Instead of complaining about the steps,
you should be thanking me for
showing you guys this rad shortcut.
Yeah, yeah, you're right.
It's still a pain in the butt.
I got your pain in the butt.
Why, you!
Dumbass, do that again, and you
get a fire arrow in your pie hole!
Brother, you got balls of steel, no joke.
Freezing!
Wowzers! Amazing!
Now aren't you cold?
Oath, sharl, raise,
bend, bard, harp, stools!
Better?
I cast a freeze resistance spell over us.
Tonki! Up here! Yeah!
Jesus!
Take it easy, Klein.
He doesn't look it, but he's a vegetarian.
Well, not exactly.
When I brought him some fish from above
ground, he scarfed it all down in one bite.
What's he doing?
He's telling you to
get on his back is all.
Dude, no way, no way in hell.
My grandpa's dying
words were don't ride in
foreign cars or on
flying Cthulhu elephants.
Is he the same dead grandpa who's dried
figs we were eating at
Dicey's the other day?
Stop farting around and get on it.
It eats me, man.
This is gonna be fun.
We're so dead.
Thanks a lot for doing this, Tonki.
All right, Tonki.
Everyone's on board, so
take us to that dungeon!
Wow.
I wonder what would happen
if you fell from way up here.
The same thing that happened
when a certain someone decided to
get to the next level of Aincrad
by climbing the Outer Pillars.
So how bad at Wonderplutz?
Care to show the lady?
Nah, I think I'll pass.
But maybe one of our more cat-like
friends would like to take a shot.
Nope, nope, nope, nope, nope.
Aaaaaaah!
Yee-haw!
Kazuto, get up here!
Check it out!
My god.
I can't believe it.
They figured out how to make
that monster fight for them.
No, there's got to be another reason.
It's not possible to tame
monsters in this game.
Not even if you're a
catsy master tamer with
a full power boost and special equipment.
Then they're leeching off the monster?
No, wait, they're not leeching.
Piggybacking?
Yeah, that's it. See,
that group's got old forearms
there doing all the heavy
lifting and sniping at the
Jelliphant when they get an opening.
But is it that easy to
control a monster's aggro?
It's ignoring everyone else.
How come they're not taking
on that forearm, dude?
Where's everyone going?
Hey, you guys, look!
What the hell's going on down there?
After what we just saw and how it went down,
it should be pretty obvious what it is.
I hate to say it, but we're looking at
that kill quest Asuna told us about.
Even though it's a quest,
helping these forearmed freaks
murder Tonki's friends is disgusting.
Damn, she's tall.
Greetings, I am Urt, Queen of the Lake!
You have bonded with my
kinsmen and I am grateful.
My two younger sisters and
I have spoken at length.
And we have a request for you.
If you would be so kind, we ask that you
save our lands from the Frost Giants?
Daddy!
She's an NPC.
There's something strange
about her, though.
Her speech pattern doesn't
follow the same set
response routines that
a normal NPC's would.
Her core programming is connected to
the language engine module of the game.
What are you saying?
Is she some kind of AI?
Yes, Daddy, she is.
In the past, Jotunheim was
similar to your Alfheim.
Covered in lush greenery
and beautiful lakes,
it basked in the blessings
of Yggdrasil, the world tree.
We, the hill giants, lived in peace and
harmony with our kinfolk, the creatures.
Far below the splendor of Jotunheim is a
realm of ice and snow known as Niflheim.
Thrimmer, king of the frost
giants, rules that land.
He shattered our peace
by casting Excalibur,
the sword that slices through wooden iron,
into the well of Oort,
the heart of our land.
It severed the thickest
roots of the world tree.
In an instant, Jotunheim lost the
blessings it received from Yggdrasil.
I was right, Excalibur.
Under Thrymmer's command,
the Frost Giants marched on Jotunheim
and overwhelmed our defenses.
Their fortresses and castles
soon blighted our land,
and scores of my people were
captured and imprisoned.
Once they seized control,
they built Thrymheim.
Their largest castle, atop the mass
of ice once known as the Well of Oort.
During the chaos, my sisters and I
escaped to the bottom of a frozen lake.
However, we no longer have
the power we once had.
The frost giants are not
satisfied with their spoils.
They wish to annihilate our kin, the
creatures that populate our realm.
If they succeed,
my powers will be extinguished, and
Thrymheim will rise to the next world,
your world, Alfheim.
Hold the phone!
You're telling us that
once they're done here,
they're going to go up and destroy Arun?
Yes, that is their intention.
King Thrymmer will seal Alfheim in ice and
continue on until he reaches
the top of Yggdrasil.
Once he reaches it, he will take
the golden apple growing there.
Thrimmer and his generals
have grown frustrated
by the time it is taking
to wipe out my kinfolk,
so they have turned to your people,
the fairies, for assistance
in their murderous plot.
Your kind hunts our kinfolk to extinction,
lured by the offer of
Excalibur as a reward.
However, King Thrymmer cannot
bestow that sword onto others.
For if Excalibur ever leaves Thrymheim,
the blessings of Yggdrasil
will return to this land,
and their castle will vanish
as a mist upon a meadow.
But then, what kind of quest is it
when the reward forward is a total lie?
How is he going to get away with it?
Most likely,
he will award the victor
a sword called Caliburn,
whose appearance is
identical to Excalibur.
But that's cheating!
If he's a king, doesn't
he have a code of honor?
Unfortunately, cheating and falsehoods
are Thrimmer's most powerful assets.
However, he has made one great mistake.
In his eagerness to slaughter my kin,
he has sent a number
of his giants down from
Thrymheim to marshal your kind for battle.
At this moment, the defenses of his castle
are weaker than they have ever been.
There's our shot.
Once the stone in the amulet turns black,
it will mean all my kinfolk have been
slain, and my powers have left me.
Good fairies, infiltrate Thrymheim,
remove Excalibur from its
plinth, and save my realm.
I am counting on you, good fairies.
This is turning into a
bigger deal than we thought.
Is this still considered a quest?
Because it's kind of...
turned into something way more
epic than a plain old quest.
You heard her.
She said if the creatures in
this world get killed off,
The Frost Giants will take over
the surface next. Yeah, I know.
But I doubt the Admins
would let that happen
without some kind of update
or warning or something.
I mean, normally, they'd let
players know a week ahead of time.
Whatever.
We're gonna finish this quest
for Tonki, right, Kazuto?
You know it.
We were gonna storm the castle
and grab Excalibur anyway.
It'll be easy if the
castle's defenses are down.
Helping Tonki and his
friends out, that's a bonus.
Here we go, guys, our last
big quest of the year.
Let's bank this thing and score us a
spot on the front page of MMO tomorrow.
Yeah!
Don't you worry, Tonki.
We'll get your home back for you.
It'll be good as new, promise.
Here we go!
Unique Loverty
I'm on my own face.
And all of you talk to me?
Hey, TV no na ka?
Hero ga mi lai no tame ni!
Iso ga shi soo!
Hoka ni wa nai.
Bi gokoji ga alu yo.
My room now.
Hitori ga Sugou Daddy no ni?
What are You Thanks?
Is You What Are Your Mother?
Are You In My Friends?
Is You What Are You?
Am I In
My Friends?
Are You In My Friends?
Here I am I'll
see you
next
time,
the King of the Giants.